Stand up tall,
reach out your hand Cut through the wind,
and make a stand The paint
within brings out a map of
your own To
the left and
the right all we saw stormy
nights All the rough winds
and waves coming day after
day And the values we had
were about to collapse Oh,
just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see is
beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and toll,
we'll go where we all wanna go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
Switch sides.
Let's all fix that kind of!
You helped me, right?
Believe me, Master, I'm ready Your
enemies shall taste my righteous fury!
General Hamlet has lost his damn mind!
No problem, Master, I'm on it!
Let me help Team Bay.
I'll handle the underlings.
And you can pound the crap
out of who's who. Hey, poker!
What the hell?
Don't worry, samurai!
I'm here to help you!
No way Snowhack can loosen us on his side!
This is the second
floor inside the castle!
The Gipters are joining the Saga Rock!
Hmm.
How peculiar.
I wonder what happened.
That was amazing, Otama!
Think Tsunami?
Your plan worked out perfectly!
You asked every Gipter on
the island to lend a paw!
They did!
And now we have a whole
zoo full of backup!
You really did save the
day, you know. Proud of you.
I'm glad you were here.
Thank you so much!
Yeah!
And we beat those dumb lizards too! Yeah!
Because we're the best!
Did that bread actually do something?
Let's go!
Muzama, look out! Run away!
No, please, no!
Go to hell!
This is the end!
you again huh judge's boy is back for more
Don't you ever say that
name in front of me again.
Now tell me how you know him.
Were you part of that mad scientist group?
What?
You mean mads?
That's ancient history.
You want to see real
science take a look at this?
I'm a cyborg boy.
I kind of figured without you
spelling it out we are so dead clean!
Is busting out his man beast?
Oh, come back, you guys!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Well, look-a-here, a cyborg expert.
See what good it does you.
Chopper, how's Mosshead?
Think he's gonna pull through this?
Oh, yes, Change.
He's gonna be alright.
Ha!
That's good.
But are you doing okay, buddy?
Ah, very kind of you to ask,
my boy, but I'll be fine.
Just tuckered out.
This form is a side effect.
I used the Rumble Ball too long.
There's a drug we could
use, but it's risky.
Hold on, at least let me heal it.
It's a medicine we minks have.
Well, anyone can use it,
but it comes from Zoe.
It heals even the most severe
wounds, and it does so rapidly.
But then,
once a bit of time has passed, he'll
suffer twice as much as he's suffering now.
I can't do it.
At the very least, I can't make
that choice while he's sleeping.
Just give me the drug already.
You, Karoo, were listening?
There's no time to debate about this.
Give me the drug so I can fight him.
Winning this battle is the
only thing that matters.
I don't care what
happens to my body later.
I need to go fight right now.
The headliners and the
gifters who went over
to the samurai army only number about 300,
but their power is considerable.
We can only assume that
the girl who got on
stage at the performance
floor is responsible.
They seem to be following her, but we
haven't been able to determine why.
There she is!
That's the brat!
You crap!
Don't look back!
Keep running!
You're gonna pay for that stunt, you punk!
Let's see how well your dirty tricks
work on our men after we kill you,
you medley little freak! Damn it!
They're not after us!
They're after Tama!
Murdering children now, huh?
Those scumbags give
decent pirates a bad name!
Don't worry, Otama! I'll protect you!
We can't leave you! I'll be fine.
You two, go ahead.
I'll catch up after I kick their butt.
Headliner coming through!
Scorpion!
Death needle!
Poison!
It's over!
The poison's already
flowing through your veins.
Thank you, Difugo!
That was great!
Yay!
Master, there you are.
Splendid work on the
operation. Now hop on.
I'll carry you from here.
Thanks, Sorcerina.
We have been doing an
awful lot of running.
Uh...
Please, take me too!
I'm begging you!
Hello there, Master!
I've come bearing news!
I've found Komachiyo!
I'm sure I'll figure it out later.
But either way, it looks like
it's time to get serious.
Blade System!
Fishman Karate!
Arabesque Rift Fist!
Shit!
And this is what you
call Iron Body, correct?
This is the fighting style
used by government agents.
The Six Powers, if I recall correctly.
I am reminded of a rumor I heard ages ago.
Something about an intelligence agent.
Someone from Cape escaping from prison.
But that's strange, don't you think?
Why would they send an
intelligence agent to prison?
Funny you'd remember
such a tiny little thing.
But yes your instincts are
right that agent it was
me do you and i know each
other because i Can't seem
to recall you at all i saw
you once but you wouldn't
have taken notice of me I
was in Cape at the time,
and you were one of the
seven warlords of the sea.
Life has taken us both in
different directions since then.
That's not a complaint, exactly.
I'm quite content with where I am now.
But you know, I suffered
a lot to get here.
All thanks to one school of 13 years ago.
I was an extraordinary talent, as
promising as the brilliant Rob Lucci.
They said you're telling me this,
but it doesn't seem to have
anything to do with me.
Shut up
I've never seen the six powers
used like that But at any
rate as I told you your tragic
past has nothing to do with me.
I i disagree you're with Straw Hat aren't
you you proudly proclaimed that you were
a member of his crew anytime someone
mentions Straw Hats name it drags up some bad
memories 13 years ago a Devil Fruit was
stolen while it was being transported on a
government ship then about two years back
when Straw Hat Luffy rose to prominence,
I received quite the surprise.
That stolen item that
caused me so much suffering
was none other than Straw
Hat's Gum-Gum fruit.
Oh, Komachiyo.
I know he'll pull through.
You're right, Onami.
Griselina, can you hurry?
Of course, Master.
Anything for you.
We'll make our way to Komachiyo
and keep him safe, too.
Wow, you guys.
Thanks for being so nice to me.
But I know it's dangerous out
there, So you two be careful.
I don't want you getting hurt.
We all have to make it back.
Because you guys are my
friends and I care about you!
She cares about us!
We'll serve our master well!
Let's go!
Komachiyo, hold on!
Make way for the master!
That power of hers is
really something else.
Yeah, she can make friends anywhere.
And powerful ones, too.
Hey!
By the way, since I'm here, what's next?
For us, I mean.
Can I be your assistant like before?
What are you talking about, Zeus?
No way! Aww!
But how about partners?
Oh, no!
Two of the Straw Hats! Cut them down!
Go away!
Don't mess with my partner!
She has him wrapped around her
little finger already Down with Kaido
The Master needs our help It's
time to lead the Samurai to victory
About 2,000 of our
fighters have changed sides
Another 2,000 were
blindsided by the betrayal
and have been defeated
by the enemy putting
that in perspective the
beast pirates initially
had 30,000 troops before losing 10,000 in
battle these losses are
in addition to the ones
I mentioned earlier so
we've lost 14,000 total
that makes it 16,000
versus 9000 if the gifters
keep this up we'll see
more white than black on
the board i don't care
which side comes out on
top as long as our escaped
convict is silenced for
good and you're certain
it's him seems to be even
if that's the case the
information he possesses
is old it poses no threat
to the government yes
but we have to set a
precedent those who escape
our organization cannot
be allowed to live well
the problem will likely
take care of itself.
He is fighting Jinbei.
This might get ugly.
Your grudge is pointless.
What does Luffy have to do with this?
I hold a grudge with the man
who stole the Gum-Gum fruit,
which is the pirate red-haired Shanks.
That bastard...
He caused me all that suffering and
doesn't even have a clue! Dammit!
Moonwalk!
Fang Tessa!
Your captain came here
wearing Shanks' Straw Hat.
Shamed me by flaunting the powers
of the stolen Gum-Gum fruit.
So of course he inherited my grudge.
What's wrong?
Haki can't block my attacks?
Actually, that's a smart decision.
Those can chew through
argument. Literally.
I'm surprised to see you move
so quickly on land. Not bad.
Fur fish me, by the way.
Is that all you've got?
Tired old racism?
I thought we were past that.
Aw, I'm sorry.
By the way, there's something
I wanted to ask you.
Fire and fire!
Time to suffer, Jinbei.
Fragless!
Fishman Jiu-Jitsu!
Low tide silver throw!
Water shot!
That hurt.
Damn, you're merciless.
Hey, time out, pal.
Can you give me a break
for just one damn minute?
There was this story I
heard when I was behind bars.
Maybe you know it as I
was being tortured the
guard mockingly told me
to pray for salvation.
Pray to the sun god Nika.
He's like a hero to slaves.
He was a legendary warrior who
fought for freedom in ancient times.
Prophesized to return and
liberate the enslaved.
I don't know if he really
existed but they say he would
deliver folks from suffering
with a smile on his face.
It was a strange story but I held on
to it in those seemingly endless days.
Doesn't matter who just save me I thought
and what answers do you
hope to find from me?
I heard a rumor about some of
the Sun Pirates you used to lead.
Quite a few of them used to be slaves.
The history of fishmen
is a history of slavery.
Turns out the guard who told me
about Nika was later executed!
I thought they might come for me next?
So I risk everything to
get the hell out of there!
Is it dangerous to speak his name?
I can't help but be curious
What are you hiding?
Tell me
Spock!
Fishman Toretti, sharp grip!
I have nothing to kill you!
Do you understand me?
What the hell?
I really struck a nerve, didn't I?
I'll crush you, my pistol!
What's gotten into you?
Fishman Karate Secret Art! Oh crap!
Hey!
That's my tail!
Demon's Brick Chest!
You heard your mouth about this
like it's some sort of game!
This is the weight of history!
You understand now!
No!